If you've landed on this page,
you're probably looking for the
perfect plan for you and maybe
you've also seen FWD's set for health
.  Welcome to this page.  I am M.
Fralipi or M. Ortigas and I am a
licensed insurance agent of FWD.  It's a good
thing you ended up here.  [music]
[music]
So set for health is a traditional plan.   This
means it has no investment
component.  You have an option here if
you want short term, long term or medium
term.  Because it has 5 years, 10 years,
and 20 years to pay options.  What if
I only paid for 5 years?  Is
the plan only for 5 years?  Am I only covered for 5 years
?  The answer is no.  Set for
health covers you until you are 75 years
old.  Why is it called the best
selling health plan?  Because number one,
you
can claim major critical
illness three times.  Number two, there are minor
critical illnesses that will not be deducted from
your major critical illness benefit.
Number three, it also includes a
life insurance benefit.
And number four, we have cashback.  What
is cashback?  Cashback is when
you reach 75 years old and you have not
had any illness or you have not
had a major critical illness,
100% of what you paid will be refunded.  'Right?  How
beautiful.
So what is the logic behind the three
times claim?  Number one,
the illness they already have could happen again
.  Do you know a relative,
friend or stranger who has had an
illness, a serious illness?  Isn't it common
for them to have recurring illnesses or
develop complications?   This is
one of the reasons why
we have a three-times claim.  Number two,
so that we have money to spend on
complications, especially when
we reach our senior years.  Then, if
you are currently employed, you probably have an
HMO or health card that will cover
all your medical bills.  But what if
you reach the age of 60 or 65?
This is the time when we retire.
This means there is no HMO benefit or maybe
our health benefit has run out.
That critical illness coverage is what
will catch us.  There is also a waiver that is
called for all those who have insurance
policies, I am sure you know what the
waiver of premium is.
This is the only benefit that
provides protection to you in case
you first develop a major critical
illness and then develop a major
disability.  If any of the two or
whichever comes first,
your plan is considered fully paid.  This
means you don't have to finish
paying because you had a major
critical illness and major disability.
So if you are worried that one
day you might develop a serious illness and be
unable to pay,
you have a claim and you have a waiver that will
cover you in case the things
we fear happen.  So what are the
illnesses covered by the set for health?  So
there are five groups, right?  So the
group one, it's all types of cancer.
In total, we have 42 critical illnesses.
So here in these groups, the three times
claim should be unrelated.  This means that
if you have already claimed in group one,
the illness that will occur after
3 years must be different.  Why 3 years?  You can't
claim one after another.
You need to have a gap of one year
for full recovery before
your illness recurs again.  Because that means
you maintain your lifestyle after
you recover.  What is a minor
critical illness?
How much is the set for health?  Because
the benefits are good.  Claim three times
and get money back.  The question is, how much is
this?  I will flash the examples
here on the screen.  So, number one, I made a
20 year plan for a 20 year old, a 20 year
plan for a 30 year old, a 10 year plan
for a 40 year old and a 10 year plan for
a 50 year old.  So look at the
difference in the premium rate per month.
As you can see, the more we use electricity
, the higher the premium.  So
why is that?  Because as we grow,
we start to feel
pain.  So the
insurance rates there are more expensive.  For a benefit of
Php1 million, this is the example.
Let's just pull out the 30 year old.  If
you can see, these are its benefits.
He has 1 million critical illness
coverage.  He has 20% minor critical
illness which is 200,000.  So if
his illness is still in the early stages,
he can file a claim right away.  So
let's take action before it gets worse.  He also has a
waiver of premium in case
he develops a serious illness or becomes disabled
.  And here in the healthy life benefit,
this is the cashback or money back.
So after 20 years, this is the amount
he will save and return to him for
additional retirement.  By the way, you
can also choose options of 5 years, 10
years, and 20 years.  So it's up to you
.  This is also based on your budget
and the time you think you can afford
to pay for the plan.  [music]
What are the things or technical
reasons why I can't
claim?  Number one, you have an
undisclosed medical history.  So
this is very important because all critical illness
coverage is contestable.
So I advise you, if you apply
for insurance, no matter which company it is,
you should declare your medical
history so that there are no problems when it
comes to claims.  Number two reason is
the illness was self-inflicted.  This
means you know you have a
liver problem but you still drink more than
the capacity.  Number three, these are
violations of the law.  are also prohibited by
our law.  This is also prohibited in insurance
because it could be a reason for
you not being able to claim.
Another reason that could be the reason
for not honoring a claim is that
you took out insurance while
you were abroad.  So it's very critical that
we sign here in the Philippines.  If
your agent is Filipino,
your place of signing must also be in the Philippines.  Another reason
is lapsed policy.  For example,
they hadn't paid their
policy for a long time and then suddenly there was a claim.
That's when they find out that
the policy hasn't been paid.  So it is
very important
that we continue to pay our
premiums to sustain the
insurance policy we have taken out.  What
if I didn't get sick,
I didn't claim to be completely healthy.
Good news.  That's our favorite
news, isn't it?  We didn't get sick.  So that
means everything you paid
for Set for Health will be refunded to you 100%.
supplement your retirement.  What age
can enroll in this plan?
Good question.  You can start here
even as a baby, 15 days old to
60 years old.
What if I already have a history?   Have
I been hospitalized or diagnosed
before?  Good news with FWD, we don't
auto decline.  You can try,
apply, we'll add the benefits
you want and we'll declare all
your medical history.  There are no
guarantees.
But at least let's try it because you know
you can still be insured if
you have a pre-existing illness.  But if
you are completely healthy, you are not
sick yet and you are in your prime years or
you don't have any symptoms yet, it's the
perfect time to get insured.  So I like
this plan.  How do I start?
If you also want a plan like this,
just message me.